exboyfriendguru.com 2010-02-15

# Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you place an order. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To process transactions

To send periodic emails

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.exboyfriendguru.com/terms.html) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.exboyfriendguru.com/terms.html>

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This policy was last modified on November 8, 2008

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Camino Marketing  
545 Belmont Ave. Suite 402  
Kitchener, Ontario N2M 5G7  
Canada

help@exboyfriendguru.com
